http://www.coolopticalillusions.com/privacy-policy/

your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Home
Gallery 1
Another Moon Illusion- The Lunar Eclipse Illusion
How to build your own impossible triangle with printable template
Funny Optical Illusion- Gray Stripe
Painted Beer Truck Illusion and Painted Pepsi Truck Illusion
The Illusion Semi-Trucks
Optical Illusion Tattoos
Looks Like a Cool Spiral, Doesn’t It?
Ambiguous
Peninsula or Horse’s Head?
Marble Columns or Shadow People
Definitely a Tree
Is This Just a Watermelon or a Real Face?
Can You Find the Hidden Sleeping Baby?
Barack Obama Optical Illusion
Who is this Man? Che-Guevara- Negative After Image Optical Illusion
Money Ambigram
Cool Optical Illusions – Amazing Optical Illusions!
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Privacy
We understand that you value your privacy. We also value your privacy and seek to explain how we use any data that we may have gathered.
Type of information we may collect:
If you complete our feedback form or interact with us, we will collect and store only the information that you knowingly provide, such as Name, Website, Email Address, and the message. This information is stored in a secure database and may also be accessible on personal computers or stored on email servers. However we currently have no intention of using this information, other than basic communication with you, or to help find relavant information that my be of interest to you (and others) on this website.
How we use your information (Google Adsense):
Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.)
Google Analytics
We do also use google analytics (and occassionally other analytics type programs). These generally gather your information along with thousands of other users, and are used mainly to decide what areas of the site to promote. To learn more about google’s privacy policy, you may do so here: Google analtyics privacy policy.
Valueclick Media
We may also use Valueclick or other vendors to provide advertising. Valueclick privacy policy.
Contact Us
If you have any specific questions about our privacy policy, please contact us.
EDITOR PICKS
How to build your own impossible triangle with printable template
How to build your own impossible triangle with printable template
POPULAR CATEGORYGallery 244Gallery 143Ambigious35Chalk Art11After Images8Wallpapers7Funny Pictures7Ambigrams5
